[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":131297,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":177985,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure t hat when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":207261,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":385256,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":9450,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":394714,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1296,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":396013,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3610,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":399624,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1011,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":400637,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get yo ur resul t.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["6","0"],"rt":13297,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":413937,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":16692,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":430631,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3665,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":434299,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</s ub> 1 =  2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1008,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":435308,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2887,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":438198,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1184,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":439385,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start  with the  first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":6492,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":445878,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1195,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":447075,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":7588,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":454664,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":2137,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":456804,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":5904,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":462709,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":2733,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":465445,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4897,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":470343,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1883,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":472228,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bi gger, yo u subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":5807,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":478037,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":5683,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":483721,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":13094,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":496822,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":16000,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":512823,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3696,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":516521,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":839,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":517362,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["4","5"],"rt":7826,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":525190,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1636,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":526829,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"Wh at is th e inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":5861,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":532692,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":987,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":533680,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2867,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":536548,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":732,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":537283,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":10073,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":547358,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":4589,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":551949,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":10386,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":562337,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</su b>. <br  /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":39588,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":601927,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":21683,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":623619,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":14513,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":638135,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":4179,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":642316,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":10872,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":653190,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is  4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":34047,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":687240,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1423,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":688666,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3855,"trial_type":"que stion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":692524,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":970,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":693495,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the rema ining qu estions as accurately as possible.","rt":97639,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":791136,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":5088,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":796234,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1018,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":797254,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["3","6"],"rt":6018,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":803274,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5041,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":808316,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4043,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":812361,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3593,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":815956,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3117,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":819075,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5. Add the two together. It is eight or less so no adjustment is needed,","response_history":["5. Add the 2 together/","5. Add the 2 together. It is 8 or","5. Add the 2 together. It is 8 o","5. Add the 2 together. It is 8 ","5. Add the 2 together. It is 8","5. Add the 2 together. It is eight","5. Add the  together. It is eight","5. Add the t together. It is eight","5. Add the two together. It is eight or less so no adjustment is needed,"],"rt":45184,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":864262,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3. I added eight and four . The su m is 12. I subtract 9, leaving my answer of 3.","response_history":["12","1","3. eight plus 4 is 12.","3. I added eight and fouer","3. I added eight and foue","3. I added eight and four. The sum is 12. I subtract 9 leaving my answer","3. I added eight and four. The sum is 12. I subtract 9, leaving my answer of 3."],"rt":74177,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":938449,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":17473,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":955930,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":6457,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":962389,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":2373,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":964763,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":6313,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":971077,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6. The inverse is the number you need to add to arrive at the identity, which is 0. Three plus six is nine. Subtract nine  to arriv e at zero. ","response_history":["6. The is","6. The inverse is the number u","6. The inverse is the number you need to add to arrive at the identity, which is 0. 3","6. The inverse is the number you need to add to arrive at the identity, which is 0. three plus 6","6. The inverse is the number you need to add to arrive at the identity, which is 0. three plus ","6. The inverse is the number you need to add to arrive at the identity, which is 0. three plus","6. The inverse is the number you need to add to arrive at the identity, which is 0. three plu","6. The inverse is the number you need to add to arrive at the identity, which is 0. three pl","6. The inverse is the number you need to add to arrive at the identity, which is 0. three p","6. The inverse is the number you need to add to arrive at the identity, which is 0. three ","6. The inverse is the number you need to add to arrive at the identity, which is 0. three","6. The inverse is the number you need to add to arrive at  the iden tity, which is 0. thre","6. The inverse is the number you need to add to arrive at the identity, which is 0. thr","6. The inverse is the number you need to add to arrive at the identity, which is 0. th","6. The inverse is the number you need to add to arrive at the identity, which is 0. t","6. The inverse is the number you need to add to arrive at the identity, which is 0. Three plus six is nine. Subtract nine to arrive at zero. "],"rt":90034,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1061114,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no. You cannot add to nine, which make zero unachievable.","response_history":["yes. Be","yes. B","yes. The reason is 2=2 2 plus 2","yes. The reason is 2=2 ","yes. The reason is 2=2 3","yes. The reason is 2 can generate any number","no. You ca nnot add  to ninewhich ","no. You cannot add to ninewhich","no. You cannot add to ninewhic","no. You cannot add to ninewhi","no. You cannot add to ninewh","no. You cannot add to ninew","no. You cannot add to nine, which make 0 ","no. You cannot add to nine, which make 0","no. You cannot add to nine, which make ","no. You cannot add to nine, which make zero unachievable."],"rt":165471,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1226594,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. You can only come up with 3 6 and zero.","response_history":["no","n","No. You can only come up with 3 6 aand zero.","No. You can only come up with 3 6 and zero."],"rt":49078,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1275682,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"I s 5 a ge nerator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes. Five plus five is ten, which comes to one. Add another five and the sum is six. Every round it goes up by one.","response_history":["Yes. two ","Yes. two","Yes. tw","Yes. t","Yes. Y","Yes. @","Yes. fi","Yes. f","Yes. Five plus five is ten, which comes to one. Add another 5","Yes. Five plus five is ten, which comes to one. Add another five and it's ","Yes. Five plus five is ten, which comes to one. Add another five and it's","Yes. Five plus five is ten, which comes to one. Add another five and it'","Yes. Five plus five is ten, which comes to one. Add another five and it","Yes. Five plus five is ten, which comes to one. Add another five and i","Yes. Five plus five is ten, which comes to one. Add another five and the sum is six. every ","Yes. Five plus five is ten, which comes to one. Add another five and the sum is s ix. ever y","Yes. Five plus five is ten, which comes to one. Add another five and the sum is six. ever","Yes. Five plus five is ten, which comes to one. Add another five and the sum is six. eve","Yes. Five plus five is ten, which comes to one. Add another five and the sum is six. ev","Yes. Five plus five is ten, which comes to one. Add another five and the sum is six. e","Yes. Five plus five is ten, which comes to one. Add another five and the sum is six. R","Yes. Five plus five is ten, which comes to one. Add another five and the sum is six. Every round it goes up by one."],"rt":134962,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1410648,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. You can only get six, three and zero.","response_history":["No. You can one","No. You can only get si x thre","No. You can only get six thr","No. You can only get six th","No. You can only get six t","No. You can only get six ","No. You can only get six, threee ","No. You can only get six, threee","No. You can only get six, three and zero."],"rt":29224,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1439881,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":11793,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1451686,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1 +_n x = n, inverse=x","response_history":["the inverse of ","the i","the ","the","th","t","1=","1+n","1+_","1+","1 +-n","1 +-","1 +_n x = n, inverse=x"],"rt":68724,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1520413,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"inverse + x = n. The inverse is the number needed to add to arrive at the identity.","response_history":["inverse =","inverse +_n ","inverse +_n","inverse +_","inverse + x = n ","inverse + x = n. The inver ","inverse + x = n. The inverse is the ne","inverse + x = n. The inverse is the number needed to arrive at ","inverse + x = n. The inverse is the number needed to  arrive at ","inverse + x = n. The inverse is the number needed to a arrive at ","inverse + x = n. The inverse is t he numbe r needed to ad arrive at ","inverse + x = n. The inverse is the number needed to add arrive at ","inverse + x = n. The inverse is the number needed to add  arrive at ","inverse + x = n. The inverse is the number needed to add to arrive at the identity."],"rt":79106,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1599528,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I think there is. I think if n is divisible by x or equal to the identity, then it is NOT a generator.","response_history":["I thinkn ","I thinkn","I think there is.,","I think there is. I this","I think there is. I think if the ","I think there is. I think if the","I think there is. I think if th","I think there is. I think if t","I  think th ere is. I think if n is divisible by x or equal to the identity, then it is NOT a generator."],"rt":66358,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1665894,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4789,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1670692,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4612,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1675308,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not  a gener ator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":13592,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1688904,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"True. This is true because once you hit a multiple of n, the system repeats.","response_history":["Yes. ","Yes.","Yes","Ye","Y","Try","True. Bec","True. Be","True. B","True. This is true because once you hit a multiple of n, the system repeats."],"rt":93290,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1782197,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14 -0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","response_history":["Sometimes","Always"],"rt":14914,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1797121,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Sometimes. One is always a generator. 2 isn't always a generator.","response_history":["Sopmetimes","Sometimes. One is always a generator. 2 isn't ale","Sometimes. One is always a generator. 2 isn't always a genet","Sometimes. One is always a generator. 2 isn't always  a gener ator."],"rt":87290,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1884418,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":21030,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1905457,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1678,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1907137,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"39","response_history":["39"],"rt":2769,"trial_type":"qu estion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1909911,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"High school diploma","response_history":["High school diploma"],"rt":2820,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1912733,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I was in a test class for a project called Elements of Math that covered everything from number theory to codes and ciphers, geometry,  calc, lo gic, etc. This started in 7th grade and we would cover subjects in weeks not months or years. It was very advanced. But, it was a long time ago.","response_history":["I was in a test class for a project called Elements of Math that covered everytinh","I was in a test class for a project called Elements of Math that covered everyting","I was in a test class for a project called Elements of Math that covered everytin","I was in a test class for a project called Elements of Math that covered everyti","I was in a test class for a project called Elements of Math that covered everything from number theory to codes and ciphers, ge","I was in a test class for a project called Elements of Math that covered everything from number theory to codes and ciphers, g","I was in a test class for a project called Elements of Math that covered everything from number theory to codes and ciphers, G","I was in a test class for a project called Elements of Math that  covered  everything from number theory to codes and ciphers, geometry, calc, logic, etc. This started in 7th gre","I was in a test class for a project called Elements of Math that covered everything from number theory to codes and ciphers, geometry, calc, logic, etc. This started in 7th grade and we would cover subject ","I was in a test class for a project called Elements of Math that covered everything from number theory to codes and ciphers, geometry, calc, logic, etc. This started in 7th grade and we would cover subjects in weeks not months or years. It was very advanced bu","I was in a test class for a project called Elements of Math that covered everything from number theory to codes and ciphers, geometry, calc, logic, etc. This started in 7th grade and we would cover subjects in weeks not months or years. It was very advanced b","I was in a test class for a project called Elements of Math that covered everything from number theory to codes and ciphers, geometry , calc,  logic, etc. This started in 7th grade and we would cover subjects in weeks not months or years. It was very advanced ","I was in a test class for a project called Elements of Math that covered everything from number theory to codes and ciphers, geometry, calc, logic, etc. This started in 7th grade and we would cover subjects in weeks not months or years. It was very advanced. But, it was a long time ago."],"rt":130231,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2042966,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"4 - used it but not often or recently","response_history":["4 - used it but not often or recently"],"rt":9341,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2052316,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"4 - used it but not often or recently","response_history":["4 - used it but not often or recently"],"rt":4667,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2056992,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4528,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2061523,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4794,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2066323,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":2279,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2068603,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":2329,"trial_type":"question ","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2070935,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":4237,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2075173,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2911,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2078085,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No.","response_history":["No."],"rt":6178,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2084264,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]